Adil Saiyad

Senior Software Developer

Energetic and curiosity-driven Android, Flutter, Xamarin and React Native developer with 8+ years of experience writing top-quality clean code for high-paced business. Eager to support in modernizing its world-class products and delivering an incredible user experience. I like to be responsible for my duties. With my best efforts, I am always ready to learn new things.

EXPERIENCE

Prioxis Technologies, Ahmedabad - Sr. Software Engineer

1st Oct 2020 - Present

Working as a Sr. Software Engineer. Worked on many projects with Native Android, Flutter, and Xamarin Forms and made it live on store.

Natrix Software Private Ltd, Surat — Sr. Software Developer

1st Aug 2019 - 30th Sep 2020

Working as a Sr Software developer. Worked on many projects which support both android and ios and make it live on store.

Sevenstar Infotech, Surat — Android Developer

1st Feb 2018 - 30th July 2019

Working as an Android developer.

Hexaware Infotech, Surat — Android Developer

1st Apr 2017 - 30th Jan 2018

As an Android developer.

Dua Infotech, Bhavnagar — Android Developer

1st Apr 2016 - 30th Mar 2017

As an Android Trainee/developer.

EDUCATION

Department of Computer Science, Bhavnagar University, Bhavnagar — Master of Computer Application

APRIL 2016

Opp Rampura petrol pump, Rampura, Surat, Gujarat- 395003 (+91) 957-495-7319 saiyadadil@gmail.com

SKILLS

Technology:

Native Android, Flutter, Core Java, C, C++,C#, Dart, JavaScript, Xamarin Forms, Native Xamarin, Basic Flutter

OS: Windows, MAC.

PROJECTS

Kalon Financial

Kalon Financial is an app that provides your financial data reports, adviser.

Trulife Financial

Digital fintech app for payroll.

1st Messenger

Chat application like whats app.

Sharjah coop

Sharjah coop is an e-commerce app..

NameArt

Dynamic App For Calligraphy fonts & Typography.

Prayer Board

App For Muslim Community.

Radhe Krishna Sticker App

Whatsapp sticker app..

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi, Gujrati.

HOBBIES

Photography, Travelling

I got 66% in MC	CA.
-----------------	-----

Shree C.O Jani BCA College - Sihor

APRIL 2014

I got 58% in BCA.

Shree M.D Patel High school Gariyadhar, Gariyadhar— HSC

MARCH 2011

I got 68% in HSC.

Shree M.D Patel High school Gariyadhar, Gariyadhar — SSC

MARCH 2009

I got 61.54% in SSC.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Full Name — Saiyad Adil Hanifbhai

DOB — 28 April 1995

Gender — Male

Marital Status — Married

Nationality — Indian

DECLARATION

 $\label{thm:continuous} \mbox{"I hereby declare that the above mentioned information is true to the best of my knowledge and belief" \\ \mbox{THANK YOU}$

ADIL SAIYAD